hockeydb.com 2019-09-12

# Privacy Policy at Hockeydb.com

The Internet Hockey Database maintains a full commitment to your privacy. Hockeydb.com does not gather personal information from anyone visiting this site, with the exception of optional information on the discussion forums. The information given there is never used for any purposes other than the discussion forums.

You may choose to post anonymously on the discussion forums. You do not have to give your e-mail, and if you do choose to give it, you can shield others from seeing it. Although e-mail addresses are stored, we do not harvest any e-mail addresses from the forum, and we will **never** make your e-mail available to any third party.

Hockeydb does not perform mass-mailings to its forum members. The only time you may receive e-mail from Hockeydb.com is when you elect to receive notification of a response to your forum topic. Such an election is opt-in -- you must actively check the box that allows an e-mail reminder to be sent to you.

From time to time cookies may be written to your computer. A cookie is simply a unique number placed on your hard drive that lets us know if you have previously been to the site. Most commercial sites such as Microsoft.com use cookies. There is no way to gather any information about you from this cookie other than knowing if you have visited the site in the past.

Hockeydb.com writes cookies under four circumstances.

  * A general cookie is written/updated for each page you visit the site. This is to count the number of pages viewed, to enable us to target advertising to your geographic location, and track the number of times you visit so that we can better understand how people use the site. Since you never give hockeydb.com any personal information this data cannot be linked to you in any way.
  * A cookie is written when you view the forum software, VBulletin. This is a canned package which uses cookies to keep track of your user ID on your computer, and to tell you which messages are new to you. It is not related to the cookie discussed above.
  * Hockeydb.com is only able to survive because of the advertising revenue it receives. Several of the banner advertising companies use cookies to track the number of ads you see, limiting you to seeing a certain number of ads per session. 
  * Hockeydb.com uses Google Analytics to analyze its site traffic. Google Analytics writes cookies to facilitate the collection of demographic-level data. No personally identifyable data is collected from hockeydb.com, and Google Analytics does not provide any personally identifyable data to Hockeydb.com

We have contracted with ValueClick and other advertising networks to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement 'click-throughs', and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, ValueClick may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. For more information about how the information is collected and used by ValueClick, please see ValueClick's privacy policy at [ http://media.valueclick.com/privacy_consumer.shtml](http://media.valueclick.com/privacy_consumer.shtml).

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [ Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

We use other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, has a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their privacy policy or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com.

If you have any questions about your privacy, please contact us
